myersbriggs.org 2019-05-09

# The Myers & Briggs Foundation - Privacy

This Statement describes The Myers & Briggs Foundation's information gathering and dissemination practices for our web services at http://www.myersbriggs.org/ and linked pages (collectively, "the Web Site" or "our Site"). By visiting our Web Site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Statement. (Revised May 30, 2018)

## Collection and Use of E-mail and User Information

The Myers & Briggs Foundation does not collect your personal information except when you knowingly provide such information as the result of the use of one or more of the features of this web site.

The Myers & Briggs Foundation maintains strict security over all information you share, and uses such information to provide you with a better web site and related services. We may share aggregate demographic information (but not data specific to any individual) with other related organizations in order for them to gain a better understanding of the traffic patterns on the Web Site.

In most cases, The Myers & Briggs Foundation will not share your contact or demographic information with entities unrelated to The Myers & Briggs Foundation, or its affiliated parties. We may, however, use such information to notify you of important changes to our Web Site or of special offers, services, or products we think you'll find valuable.

## The information we collect from those who visit our website

This website uses cookies, which are necessary to its functioning and required to achieve the purposes illustrated in this privacy policy. These functional cookies are required for your security and your user experience. The information we gather through the use of tracking technologies is aggregated and cannot be matched with any personally identifiable information about you.

You can decline cookies at any time if your browser allows you to do this. Depending on your browser's settings, you will receive a notification that our server wants to place a cookie with a particular lifespan on your computer. However, we would like to point out that it will be impossible for you to use our order system if you decline functional cookies.

Whenever our cookies contain personal data, we expressly inform you and ask for your consent (opt-in) before saving the cookie to your computer.

## Diagnostic Problems

We may use your Internet address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Web Site.

## Guidelines Regarding Children

Personal information about children is a concern for all of us. At The Myers & Briggs Foundation, we take the protection of children's privacy very seriously. We do not encourage participation or visitation of our Site by children. If you are under thirteen, you may only use this Web Site with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

## Customer Information

The Myers & Briggs Foundation has numerous security measures in place to protect you from the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We request you not include any credit card information in e-mail correspondence with The Myers & Briggs Foundation.

The Myers & Briggs Foundation reserves the right to disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with the legal process, response to claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of The Myers & Briggs Foundation's Board of Directors, its employees, customers, clients, or the general public.

Other than as described above, The Myers & Briggs Foundation does not sell, rent, or provide access to information about its clients and customers to third parties.

## Contact Information

If you have questions about this Privacy Statement or anything else about our Web Site, you can contact us at the following e-mail address: [coordinator@myersbriggs.org](mailto:coordinator@myersbriggs.org)
